clickcompare.info 2007-10-15

# Price Comparison Shopping - Click.Compare.Buy.Save

### General Information

At www.clickcompare.info we respect the privacy of our users and follow a strict privacy policy. This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information which we may receive via the web site located at www.clickcompare.info, and is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details.

### Personal User Data

The only ways in which www.clickcompare.info may receive personally identifiable information about you is if you knowingly and willingly provide the information by contacting us using email or through of our service areas, including, but not limited to, contests and promotions. In such areas, the information you disclose is done so knowingly and willingly, at your sole discretion. The personally identifiable information you disclose is optional, and is normally required so as to effectively enter you into any contest we may offer or to reply to your email and correspondence. www.clickcompare.info will never share the aggregate results of the data it receives with advertisers or any other forms of internet activities. We are committed to user privacy protection and will keep everything secure as stated in the Data Protection Act, 1998.

### Standard User Data

The standard data we collect about our users is not personally identifiable information, meaning it is not information which identifies them as an individual. By using any of www.clickcompare.info services or reading its content, you agree that you understand the nature this data collection. When you log onto www.clickcompare.info, certain standard information is normally collected by our servers. This information may include, but may not be limited to, the location or website from which you came, the time you spend on parts of www.clickcompare.info or its related sites, the software you use to browse the Internet (for example Microsoft Internet Explorer), the amount of information you access from www.clickcompare.info and quantity of pages downloaded. This data collection is standard and common to most websites on the Internet. This information does not identify you as an individual, and none of this information will be disclosed in any form that is specific to you as a user of www.clickcompare.info.

### Cookies

Parts of www.clickcompare.info use cookies to better provide our services and information. On the Internet, a "cookie" is file that a website transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. This is a common feature of many websites on the Internet, and is employed by www.clickcompare.info to better serve to you our services and content. The cookie is stored on your own computer (not our servers) and file that is stored on your computer is small in size and does not identify you personally.

To prevent cookies from tracking you as you navigate our Web sites, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note that some portions of our Web sites may not work properly if you refuse cookies. 

### Further Policy

It is a www.clickcompare.info policy that we will not disclose personally identifiable information you may choose to submit to www.clickcompare.info to any third parties. We follow a strict policy of no 'spam' and no sales of personally identifiable information.

### Children

We welcome users of all ages to our content and services. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), we do, however, specifically request that you have the permission of your parents or legal guardian to view any content at www.clickcompare.info and to take part in any and all services we offer, as we cannot and will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users.

### Notes to Parents

We respect that you may wish to monitor the content and services your child uses on the Internet. If you wish for your child to be removed from any and/or all www.clickcompare.info services, please send an email specifically requesting your wish to [admin@clickcompare.info](mailto:admin@clickcompare.info). Please note, however, that while we will subsequently use our best endeavours to prevent your child from using our services, we cannot and will not be held responsible for access to our services your child may subsequently gain, as this is out of our control.
